We are going to be spending the next seven
days in this massive underground city.
How does this place exist?
Although it may look like
something straight out of the future,
this city is built inside a mine,
dating back over a thousand years ago
and with countless uncharted
tunnels and chambers.
Who knows what horrors we’ll run into.
These are the stairs
that descend into the city.
How old are these stairs?
Older than us.
All right, now that we're down here.
Look at how high up the ceiling is.
We are 400ft underground right now
and somehow this village just exists.
This is nuts.
During World War Two, when
Romania was getting bombed,
thousands of people would hide here.
And now just a bunch
of YouTubers live here.
And soon enough, we found a
solid place to spend the night.
I think we should camp here.
You're the boss.
Our stuff is all
the way up there.
So with home base decided,
we went up to grab our bags
and using all our
collective brainpower,
we discovered the best way
to get them down to camp.
Oh! That's awesome.
That’s dead on!
We just finished fishing
everything out of the water
Our food for the challenge
consists of bagged food,
and we each brought
a personal bag.
What's in yours Karl?
Let's look at somebody else's.
You get the point.
You guys want to know
what the craziest part is?
We've barely seen any
of this underground city.
The walls that surround us
are hiding a bunch of tunnels.
There's even a chamber as
massive as the one we’re in now.
Where?
What?
However, what these guys
don't know is that every single day
I'm bringing a famous YouTuber
to help us explore these tunnels.
But the more YouTubers that joined us,
the deeper this city would fall into chaos.
You just got here, bro.
We're going to bed
at a reasonable hour
because I have a big
surprise in the morning.
That's ominous
Day one in the underground city was a
success. We'll see you in the morning.
Good morning.
bro why?
It's gonna be a great day.
First thing in the morning, I took everyone
to the elevator for my big announcement.
Starting today, every single morning, a
famous YouTuber is going to be joining us.
Our surprise guest, coming
down from the surface
is JiDion!
Welcome to the underground city.
This is legit a city.
There's even a Ferris wheel here.
Yeah, but that's not all.
So we have not been up these stairs yet,
and is not that the most ominous
stairs you've ever seen in your life?
Boys, come up here.
Lazarbeam has a fear of heights.
Why are we doing this to me?
Today we're conquering
your fear of heights.
Oh my gosh.
How are you so calm?
If I'm gonna die, I'm gonna
die, I'm not gonna worry about it.
Oh, God.
All right, we have a
lantern to go exploring.
I feel so much safer now.
Well, don't get too comfortable,
because just around the corner,
we found this menacing door.
Access forbidden.
Oh heck no
- Wait.
- I'll check it out.
Oh no, no, no.
Alright guys, looks safe!
Are we sure there's not like people
living down here or something?
Only one way to find out.
This does feel like
a very haunted area.
Oh, no.
These boards either held up a sign that
said don't enter that someone ripped down
It definitely did.
Or they're just
here for decoration.
I think they're here for
decoration. Follow me!
This doesn’t look creepy at all.
Hey everyone, for 1000 years they've
harvested salt from the salt mine.
This is a dark chocolate
sea salt Feastables bar.
Hear me out. What if we put
more salt on our sea salt bar?
Straight from the source.
That's so good.
It tastes really good.
And for climbing
multiple sets of stairs.
Where is this leading us?
I'm not sure.
Going where we
probably shouldn't.
Wait. What does
this say? Do not pass.
What does that mean?
Karl, put your hands like this.
Dude.
We probably can't
put this on camera.
As eerie as these tunnels were,
the creepiest were still yet to come as
we ventured back to camp for the night.
As you can see,
JiDion joined us in the bed-ring.
Tomorrow's gonna be a fun day.
We have a super special guest.
We’ll see you in the morning.
Alright. It's the start of day three,
and you know what that means.
Let's go see who the special
guest of the day is. Send them down!
I see a shadow!
There he is!
Is it Kai?
Maybe it’s Speed?
I see two shadows!
There's two of them?!
Today the two guests are!
Sam and Colby!
Yeah!
If you don't know already,
Sam and Colby specialize in exploring
abandoned and haunted places,
so it'll be interesting
to see what they think
when we explore this
1000 year old tunnel system.
Are we going?
See how high the ceiling is?
Well apparently, there's like a
window where you can look down
and I want to see Lannan’s reaction
because he's terrified of heights.
Meanwhile, the others are
going to upgrade our base camp.
Alright, alright, you’ll do stuff here,
and then you'll do stuff over there.
Oh I get it, you're
a supervisor.
Yeah!
Yeah. Has no clue what's
going on and tells us what to do.
Alright, let's get to
work. Let's get to work.
As we went deeper than before,
I never could have guessed how
sketchy exploring these tunnels would get.
I think Sam and Colby should lead the
way because they have more experience
We love creepy holes, you know?
That makes sense.
Yeah, lead the way.
You're getting farther
and farther away.
I'm right behind you.
Oh, we got two ways.
This way.
Karl!
I got Colby so good
That scared the crap out of him.
Anyway, we kept walking until we eventually
came across this ominous staircase.
This is sketch!
There's just a
gigantic cross up here.
Wait wait wait, really?
What do we make of this cross?
The one thing that we
know about these salt mines
is there is a legend that
there was one spirit seen,
and they created an
altar at that location
because it's where the
hauntings are, this is the spot.
That sounds awesome!
Let's keep going!
Yo, that’s the hole
that leads to the camp.
Oh, is that the hole?
I feel like there's a
fence for a reason.
Should I go over there?
I’ll watch from here.
Dude, I can see our camp!
Look!
Shawn!
Oh, they're way up above us.
How's it going?
We have a shower boys!
They just yelled
we have a shower.
How did you do that?
First we'll make a shower head out of
the cap and then we'll hang our water jug.
Lannan! Come check this out!
I'm coming.
Lannan, you can't be
this afraid of heights.
I'm coming bro, I'm
coming. This is okay.
No, no, no.
No one touch me.
We're overcoming our fears.
Having now explored
50% of the mines
and with a way to
wash our reeking bodies,
this underground
city was finally thriving.
But there was still plenty to do
because by the next
morning, we had to welcome
our day four special guest
coming down the elevator!
Wait they’re short!
Is the biggest Twitch streamer
on the planet,
Kai Cenat!
Welcome to the underground city!
Alright Kai I want you to jump
and stomp as loud as you can.
What the heck?
Kai now that you’re
here, we have a big family.
And nothing's gonna
get between any of us.
Is that foreshadowing?
Bro, you just got here!
Oh God!
Kai, I specifically saved
one secret tunnel for you.
So let’s go explore it!
So using these boats, we
crossed the underground lake.
That's right, a lake,
that's underground.
And on the other side, our next set of
tunnels was through this hole in the wall.
Karl should go first.
I'll go first.
There's a door in the hole.
What is behind that door?
We got to get in
there, that is awesome.
You got it, you got it, you got
it, you got it. Oh my God.
So after a boost from Shawn
we were ready to explore
- See you Shawn!
- Bye Shawn!
I see this in movies all the time. When
we get past the door, we're gonna die.
What's the game plan?
You gotta go straight,
then you gotta make a left,
then right is always right,
so make that U-turn half circle
opposite of your left hand side.
But once you go straight,
you take five steps back. Okay?
So after trekking through
this sketchy tunnel...
What happened? What?
It literally just opened
up into a giant dark void.
They told me there was another
cavern just as big as the other one,
so I thought it'd be fun if we
brought the world's brightest flashlight.
- Dude
- What?
This is unreal!
Hey wait, be careful
there are ledges here
Yeah I'm gonna jump.
Wait you're gonna jump?
Bye guys!
Kai where are you going?
Bye!
If it’s safe for him...
Yeah this is cool!
- Together!
Hello!
It sounds like I’m over there!
Now they're all down there
in the middle of the cavern,
I’m gonna turn the
flashlight off to scare them.
Ready?
- Hey!
- What we doing.
Come on! Come on!
They're leaving us.
Hurry! Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Lock them in!
He's leaving us!
Oh God!
Later nerds!
Open it!
You’re gonna break Karl’s arm!
Pull! Pull!
I’m letting go.
Hey man!
What?
What’s what?
Is y’all trying to leave us?
No!
I heard you say “later losers”
Who?
You!
No...
He tried to trap us
in there for a night.
No no, you can stay down there.
So with tensions running high
after a long day of exploring,
we decided to turn in for the night,
but Karl was about to strike again
and this time with JiDion’s help.
We're going to prank
the rest of the team.
Everyone's asleep right now.
We're gonna have this mannequin standing on
the bridge and have a speaker behind him.
We’re gonna play Kai’s song
"Bustdown Rollie Avalanche."
We ready?
I think we’re...
Are we being attacked?
They’re playing my song
That’s your song?
Yes.
See that light over there?
All the way at the top?
At least it’s a good song though
Whoever has done this has
made a great enemy in their life.
What are you gonna do
tomorrow to get your revenge?
Oh boy.
I will dedicate my entire
life to their destruction.
I will wipe them and their
entire family from existence.
Lines are being drawn,
enemies are being formed.
These last few days
are gonna be interesting.
I'm gonna try to go back to bed.
I'm the only one
awake right now.
Everyone is still asleep
after what Karl did last night.
I think our guest is about to arrive.
They're coming down right now.
- Yo. What’s good, bro?
- It’s Logan Paul.
Usually Jimmy's here to give a
tour, but he's asleep right now.
- You can go wake him up.
- Oh, I'm going to do that.
Yeah, you want to go do that.
Good morning Logang!
What's poppin’?
Chandler’s excited to
see you man, I can tell.
Our day five guest is
WWE superstar Logan Paul.
Let's go.
This video is just me seeing how
many famous people I can drag in this pit.
Hey, guys. You know
someone who's not here?
Karl. JiDion.
Last night, it was Karl and JiDion
just like running pranks on us
and I think I can speak for everyone
here, they’re getting exiled today.
This was Karl’s bed he
wont be using this anymore.
Hope where he’s sleeping
now is comfortable.
I was sick of that guy anyway.
Alright, LazarBeam’s
going a little crazy.
One final thing, I
think Karl is still asleep.
We're going to go wake him up.
Wakey, wakey.
Oh my god.
I just woke up to Logan Paul.
Karl, I got a surprise for you.
You might be a bit sleepy,
but just come up here, buddy.
So I threw your
bed into the water.
Dude I hate this
underground city, bro.
With the prank war actually
started to bother some people,
Kai decided to step up and
become the mayor of the city.
Does anybody object
of me being mayor?
I vote that the shortest
person here be the mayor.
I don't object.
To establish some
order in the city
Mayor Kai first punished JiDion
and Karl for last night's prank
and I've got to warn you,
with this city's population having
grow to now nine YouTubers,
everything you're gonna witness
from here on out is just pure chaos.
Alright, you’ll sleep
in the elevator.
Elevator?
If they’re in the elevator,
how do we get up?
We gotta take 15 flights of stairs, Kai?
You're not thinking!
Bro! You just got here, bro!
- You just got here last night.
- Bro!
Why is he the mayor?
I'm just gonna say it.
Alright, we need to start
acting on these orders.
You guys, go ahead and
carry your stuff to the elevator.
Enjoy your dictatorship.
Hey, enjoy your elevator.
Yeah, enjoy your
elevator, buddy.
Bro, me laying down this
way is looking like a penthouse.
And me laying like
this is still an elevator.
Now that the criminals are
gone, Kai, what do you want to do?
First things first.
I think we should have a place just
for storage.
It should go right there.
So just to clarify, we're moving
our belongings away from our beds
for no reason.
No, because Kai told us.
Honestly, this does nothing. Now
we just have to work for our clothing.
Alright, maybe making Kai
Mayor wasn't such a great idea.
So after doing some more
of Kai's ridiculous demands,
the day one boys and I set
off on our daily exploration.
Alright, we’ll be
back in like two hours.
So while we've explored just about every
tunnel and room in this underground city,
I have a special one here
that I really want to show you.
- You see this dead end right here?
- Yeah.
What if I told you
it's a fake dead end?
No!
Dude, what is this?
There you go.
What?!
There's a fake door
that led to a giant tunnel!
Where's the
tunnel lead to though?
Let's find out.
Alright, get this, the tunnel was so
long, we literally had to run down it.
It’s still going!
This is the longest tunnel
I've ever seen in my life.
I see the light.
And at the end of the tunnel
is a Zaxby's!
That I built.
Yo!
Brand new MrBeast Box
available in every single Zaxby's
that comes with the Feastables bar.
And meanwhile, back at camp, the other
boys had way too much time on their hands.
I think we move all their
beds to the bridge bro.
That's the day one bridge.
This is the new gens.
Let’s do it. Let's go.
I got Jimmy’s.
And then I'll grab Lazar’s.
I've never been this
happy in my entire life.
The MrBeast Box
comes with great chicken,
your favorite sides from Zaxby's,
and it's about to
disappear forever
so if you haven't
tried it, go get it now.
Zaxby's also has a ton of sauces.
This is good.
This is good sauce.
Yeah, right here.
Perfect.
For the first 30 days in October,
we're giving away $10,000 in a random
drawing for people who buy Feastables
and on Halloween night, we're
giving one lucky winner $1 million.
Just post a photo of you holding a
Feastables bar and tag Feastables.
The Feastables bars
in these MrBeast boxes
can also be used to
enter into the giveaway.
I'm so happy right now.
Don't miss out. Go get yourself a MrBeast
box from Zaxby's while you still can.
I think we're all
on the same page.
The other people in the city
do not need to know about this.
We did not eat Zaxby’s.
Now, what I failed to realize
is what would happen when you
leave a bunch of content creators alone,
with nothing to do for hours.
Why do you guys
have ski masks on?
While you guys were gone, we made
sure that we made this a better city.
So we’re gonna have a town hall meeting
to discuss the new changes that we've made.
- Okay.
- All right.
This better be good.
- Are you guys ready?
- Kai, what the heck is going on?
Welcome to York New City.
This is our current state.
Everything is just so messy.
It looks bad, right?
Go to the next slide.
We let the new gen
sleep here from now on.
So what about the day one-ers?
You guys are now on the bridge.
But we have a master bedroom.
Somebody is
sleeping on the raft.
Alright, I think
I've seen enough.
Day one-ers come on, come
on. I'm taking my day one-ers.
Come on, come on, let's go.
Have fun. Yo, where y’all going?
No, we can't let him get
back to the base before us.
You’re right.
No, no, no!
Shawn, stop them! Shawn!
No!
Kai, we all wanted to talk
to you about something.
What?
You've turned into a dictator.
- What?
- Honestly, really quickly.
We’ve got to move
our beds over here.
I quit bro!
I hate being mayor bro.
You gotta make all the rules up
and stuff and everybody gotta follow it.
I almost broke my neck.
You good? As a show of
peace, I brought you some food.
If you guys follow me here,
I brought all of you Lunchly’s.
I get a Prime and Feastables?
Nice, the cheese
tastes like actual cheese.
It's good.
Fire.
It actually is so good.
So after a day of
establishing a new leader,
toppling a corrupt government,
and then becoming friends again,
we decided to call it a night.
Alright.
Good night, you hooligans.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Good morning everybody.
Will everyone please
meet me at the elevator.
Who do you guys think the next
inhabitant of the underground city is?
I think it's IShowSpeed. He's literally
streaming right now in Romania.
It's the entire Sidemen.
Could be Jynxzi.
All right, let's see who it is.
That’s Speed. That’s
Speed, I can tell.
Send them down!
That’s a massive box.
It's a girl.
Oh, it could be a girl.
Our day six special guest of
the seven days underground city.
All right, here we go.
What is that gigantic box?
Lannan you're going to be excited for this
box. All your favorite things are in here.
- Which way do you want me to open it?
- Just open it.
Let’s go!
For day six, we actually have
two guests. Vikkstar and Speed.
So boys, welcome to
the underground city.
Yeah, we've done this tour like
6 or 7 times at this point right?
Alright, follow me, boys.
If you guys want, we can hit
the highest point of this cave.
As long as you promise
me you won't jump.
It's not too high though.
Wait, is that water?
- Do not jump, bro.
- It’s water, though.
No! Stop! Stop!
I ain’t gonna lie bro, I love y'all,
but y'all stink. You stink, I promise.
Hey Speed!
Dude, y'all stink I'm
not even playing, bro.
You just look like you stink.
I just took a shower.
There's no showers here, though.
You'll see.
- Stop lying.
- Oh my God.
You're lying! Bro, your lying!
Stop lying!
That's must! It's must!
How do you smell?
Lift it up.
Dude, get out of there.
Is that Old Spice?
Yes. You know!
Good move, stinky boy. Get
your hands away from me.
And unsurprisingly, the first thing
Vikkstar and Speed wanted to check out
was the underground
soccer arena.
Y’all played a game
yet or no in here?
- No.
How have you not played a game?
What have you been doing for seven days?
Blue is on a team. Chandler,
Speed, Logan over here.
- Y’all got all the athletes.
- Vikky sucks!
Bro, thats a stacked team!
It's even. All
right, let's do it.
Come on, Speed. Come
on, Speed. Whats up?
Go back! Jidion, Jidion.
Kick it! Punt it!
I have...
Keep scoring!
Kick it as hard as you can! Go ahead!
Blue team won.
Blue teams won. Let's
keep the tour going.
As we were going to
check out the golf course,
we caught something on
camera never seen before.
We caught Logan
without Prime. It's so weird.
Don’t put that in.
After soccer, we
played some golf,
which, honestly, Lazar
could use some practice with.
I'll give you $100 if
you get a hole in one.
- Right here?
- Yup.
We even climbed the
massive Ferris wheel.
You do some dumb stuff
when your bored, huh?
If I get injured, the WWE
is going to be pissed.
So will my fiancé, though.
I'm going to be a dad. What
am I doing up here, dude?
We also projected a video
game on the cave wall.
We’re creating
history right now.
We're the first ones that ever play
in here.
Hole too big! Hole too big!
And lastly, we climbed
to the very top of this cave
just to play the most insane
game of catch you've ever seen.
The only thing stopping
us from falling is this wood.
It’s not even stable.
Let's get in position,
boys. Let's get in position.
Yo, Lazar, try to catch
this Feastables bar.
Here we go. Here we go.
It's a parachute.
And just for you to understand
how high up we were,
it took nearly ten entire seconds for
our Feastables to reach the ground.
Oh, that is coming
down. Oh, God.
Alright, dropping
some marshmallows.
Here they come!
Catch it.
I see them! One! Two! Karl!
Dude, it's so close.
Hey, Logan. Got a
Prime bottle for you.
- You got it, you got it.
- You got it.
Come on, baby!
Let’s go!
Of course, when it's
Prime, he catches it.
And for the last
night in the city,
we made a campfire in the
amphitheater to wind down.
All right everybody, what was
your favorite part of the video?
Well, it's actually
going to be leaving.
I enjoyed the friends I made.
Yeah.
I enjoyed toppling
the dictatorship.
Why is he the mayor?
Enjoy your dictatorship.
I quit bro!
It's too much work.
My favorite part was just dragging all
these YouTubers to the middle of nowhere,
deep underground, and forcing them
to hang out with me. It was a lot of fun.
I'm grateful for you all coming out.
Thank you so much.
And boys, with only one day
left in this underground city,
we've really started
to fill this room up.
All right, cut the lights off.
We'll see you
tomorrow for day seven.
All right, guys, good night.
- Good night.
- Good night everybody.
What a wonderful day!
Time to go home.
Please hurry.
And after we cleaned
up the entire camp,
it was finally time to
leave this underground city.
This was fun.
I'm gonna miss all of you.
I just got here why
is everyone leaving?
I've been here forever.
I can't wait to leave.
Our first time seeing
sunlight.
In a week!
Ah, it's so bright, dude.
Oh my God.
Now go outside and
touch some grass yourself.